(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{23:function(e,n,t){},31:function(e,n,t){"use strict";t.r(n);var r,o,i,s,S,a,p,c,E=t(0),A=t.n(E),D=t(14),d=t.n(D),u=t(5),l=(t(23),t(4)),h=t(2),I=h.b.button(r||(r=Object(l.a)(["\n    border: 1px solid #616A94;\n    border-radius: 50px;\n    padding: 15px 30px;\n    text-decoration: none;\n    color: #616A94;\n    background-color: #161A31;\n    transition: 0.3s;\n    font-size: 1em;\n    cursor: pointer;\n    outline: none;\n\n    &:hover {\n        color: white;\n        background-color: #616A94;\n    }\n"]))),b=I,O=t(1),j=h.b.div.withConfig({displayName:"Start__Intro",componentId:"sc-1emqe5i-0"})(["margin-top:8em;text-align:center;"]),m=Object(h.a)(o||(o=Object(l.a)(["\n    margin-top: 2em;\n"]))),w=Object(h.b)(b).withConfig({displayName:"Start___StyledButton",componentId:"sc-1emqe5i-1"})(["",""],m),f=function(e){var n=e.props;return Object(O.jsxs)(j,{children:[Object(O.jsx)("h1",{children:"Which Block Cipher is the right fit for you?"}),Object(O.jsx)("h4",{children:"A questionnare to help decide on the right block cipher for your needs and purposes."}),Object(O.jsx)(w,{onClick:function(){return n(!0)},children:"Begin"})]})},x=h.b.h1(i||(i=Object(l.a)(["\n    margin-top: 4em;\n    font-size: 48px;\n"]))),g=h.b.p(s||(s=Object(l.a)(["\n    font-size: 24px;\n    margin-bottom: 3em;\n"]))),N=function(e){var n=e.pts,t=[];for(var r in n)t.push([r,n[r]]);return t.sort((function(e,n){return n[1]-e[1]})),Object(O.jsxs)(O.Fragment,{children:[Object(O.jsx)(x,{children:"The 3 best block cipher choices for you are:"}),Object(O.jsxs)(g,{children:["1: ",t[0][0]]}),Object(O.jsxs)(g,{children:["2: ",t[1][0]]}),Object(O.jsxs)(g,{children:["3: ",t[2][0]]}),Object(O.jsx)(I,{onClick:function(){return window.location.reload()},children:"Retry"})]})},T=h.b.div(S||(S=Object(l.a)(["\n    text-align: center;\n    font-size: clamp(20px, 2.5vw, 24px);\n    margin-top: 10vh;\n"]))),y=h.b.div(a||(a=Object(l.a)(["\n    display: flex;\n    flex-direction: column;\n    width: 70%;\n    margin: 2em auto;\n\n    @media screen and (min-width: 1180px) {\n        width: 50%;\n    }\n"]))),M=h.b.button(p||(p=Object(l.a)(["\n    display: block;\n    border: 1px solid #616A94;\n    border-radius: 15px;\n    padding: 15px 30px;\n    text-decoration: none;\n    color: #616A94;\n    background-color: #161A31;\n    transition: 0.3s;\n    font-size: 1em;\n    outline: none;\n    user-select: none;\n    margin-top: 1em;\n    cursor: pointer;\n    \n    @media screen and (min-width: 1180px) {\n        &:hover {\n            color: white;\n            background-color: #616A94;\n        }\n    }\n"]))),R=h.b.div(c||(c=Object(l.a)(["\n    width: 70%;\n    margin: 0 auto;\n"]))),v=[{question:"What type of device would you want secured?",options:[{answer:"Low computing resources (resource-constrained)",points:{DES:0,AES:200,SIMON:100,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:100,RSA:0}},{answer:"High computing power/resources (unrestrained)",points:{DES:100,AES:100,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:0,RSA:100}}]},{question:"Is having the industry standard the most important for you?",options:[{answer:"Yes",points:{DES:100,AES:500,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:150}},{answer:"No",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:200,TDES:0,IDEA:200,Serpent:0,RSA:0}}]},{question:"Do you need a cipher that offers customizability for key sizes?",options:[{answer:"Yes",points:{DES:0,AES:200,SIMON:200,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:200,RSA:200}},{answer:"No",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}}]},{question:"Is the speed of encryption/decryption important for your application?",options:[{answer:"Yes",points:{DES:100,AES:300,SIMON:150,TDES:0,IDEA:250,Serpent:200,RSA:0}},{answer:"No",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}}]},{question:"What block size fits your application needs?",options:[{answer:"64",points:{DES:200,AES:300,SIMON:300,TDES:300,IDEA:300,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"128",points:{DES:0,AES:300,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:300,RSA:0}},{answer:"256",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"Variable",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:300,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}}]},{question:"Would you require only patented ciphers?",options:[{answer:"Yes",points:{DES:100,AES:100,SIMON:100,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:0,RSA:100}},{answer:"No",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:100,RSA:0}}]},{question:"What data type would your application require screening?",options:[{answer:"Transfer Protocols",points:{DES:0,AES:100,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"Digital Data",points:{DES:100,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"Internet of Things",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:100,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"Hardware",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:100,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}},{answer:"Stream Data",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:50,RSA:0}}]},{question:"What information would your applicaiton be securing?",options:[{answer:"Highly Sensitive Data (passwords, private personal info, etc.)",points:{DES:0,AES:200,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:0}},{answer:"Less important/non-private data",points:{DES:50,AES:100,SIMON:50,TDES:50,IDEA:50,Serpent:50,RSA:50}}]},{question:"What data type would your application require screening?",options:[{answer:"Brute Force",points:{DES:0,AES:100,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:100,RSA:200}},{answer:"Exhaustive Search",points:{DES:0,AES:200,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:0,Serpent:100,RSA:200}},{answer:"Eavesdropping",points:{DES:100,AES:100,SIMON:100,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:100}},{answer:"Meet-in-the-middle (Biclique attack)",points:{DES:0,AES:50,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:200}}]},{question:"Does the hardware your application run on have AES hardware acceleration (ex: Intel AES-NI)?",options:[{answer:"Yes",points:{DES:0,AES:300,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:0}},{answer:"No",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0}}]},{question:"The prominence/relevance of different ciphers can indicate how many attacks/cryptnalysis strategies have been attempted and analysed against it. Is this vital or are more experimental but still theoretically proven ciphers alright as well?",options:[{answer:"More experimental is fine!",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:100,TDES:0,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:0}},{answer:"No I'd rather have more established ciphers",points:{DES:100,AES:200,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:100}}]},{question:"Would you want to make use of asymmetric or symmetric encryption?",options:[{answer:"More experimental is fine",points:{DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:100,TDES:0,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:0}},{answer:"No I'd rather have more established ciphers",points:{DES:100,AES:200,SIMON:0,TDES:100,IDEA:100,Serpent:100,RSA:100}}]}],q={DES:0,AES:0,SIMON:0,TDES:0,IDEA:0,Serpent:0,RSA:0},k=function(){var e=Object(E.useState)(v),n=Object(u.a)(e,2),t=n[0],r=(n[1],Object(E.useState)(0)),o=Object(u.a)(r,2),i=o[0],s=o[1],S=Object(E.useState)(q),a=Object(u.a)(S,2),p=a[0],c=a[1],A=function(e){var n=e.target.getAttribute("data-index"),t=v[i].options[n].points,r={DES:p.DES+t.DES,AES:p.AES+t.AES,SIMON:p.SIMON+t.SIMON,TDES:p.TDES+t.TDES,IDEA:p.IDEA+t.IDEA,Serpent:p.Serpent+t.Serpent,RSA:p.RSA+t.RSA};c(r),s(i+1)};return Object(E.useEffect)((function(){}),[]),Object(O.jsxs)(T,{children:[t[i]&&Object(O.jsxs)(O.Fragment,{children:[Object(O.jsx)(R,{dangerouslySetInnerHTML:{__html:t[i].question}}),Object(O.jsx)(y,{children:t[i].options.map((function(e,n){return Object(O.jsx)(M,{"data-index":n,dangerouslySetInnerHTML:{__html:e.answer},onClick:A},n)}))})]}),12===i&&Object(O.jsx)(N,{pts:p})]})};var z=function(){var e=Object(E.useState)(!1),n=Object(u.a)(e,2),t=n[0],r=n[1];return Object(O.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz",children:t?Object(O.jsx)(k,{}):Object(O.jsx)(f,{props:r})})},C=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&t.e(3).then(t.bind(null,32)).then((function(n){var t=n.getCLS,r=n.getFID,o=n.getFCP,i=n.getLCP,s=n.getTTFB;t(e),r(e),o(e),i(e),s(e)}))},_=t(18);d.a.render(Object(O.jsx)(A.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(O.jsx)(_.a,{children:Object(O.jsx)(z,{})})}),document.getElementById("root")),C()}},[[31,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.5bc9e586.chunk.js.map